heyitsfree.net 2017-02-01

# Privacy Policy • Hey, It's Free!

Hey, It’s Free! (further referenced as “HIF,” “our,” or “we”) is for entertainment purposes only. However, we strive to protect our readers (further reference as “you,” “users,” or “readers”) privacy in every way possible.

 **Freebies**

All offers listed on HIF are available to our readers to the best of our knowledge at the time of publication. HIF is not responsible for any damages caused either directly or indirectly as a result of using links provided on the site. HIF is also not responsible for any misprints, incorrect information, typographical errors, or omissions in any of the content, material and free offers listed. We are, however, responsible for being funny and/or witty and claims full responsibility for making you laugh.

HIF does not send out any free merchandise, nor do we guarantee, approve or endorse any offers listed. We simply find free stuff, contests and coupons then list them for your convenience. HIF is not responsible for the shipment of goods and/or services. We make no guarantees as to the quality or value of the products or services offered from our advertisers. If you have any problems or questions about a freebie, please contact the original vendor that shipped the freebie.

Please make sure you have read any fine print and / or restrictions carefully before you sign up for, purchase, accept, or enter any offer. It is your responsibly to be cautious when giving personal information online.

If a freebie or link is posted on HIF and misrepresents the offer, please [contact us](http://www.heyitsfree.net/contact) and we will remove the content in question.

 **Information Collected About You**

While visiting our site, the following information is collected and stored:

  * Your IP address
  * All pages located on HIF that you visited
  * The length of time spent browsing our site

Furthermore, if you choose to leave a comment, the following information is also stored:

  * Your name
  * Your email address

We do _not_ record nor store any personal information, such as but not limited to your home address, full name, birthdate, or telephone numer.

Any information that we collect is _never_ shared with, sold, rented, leased, or traded to any outside 3rd party. The information is only used for administrative and technical purposes by employees of HIF.

 **3rd Party Advertising and Cookies**

Advertising on HIF is handled through Google Adsense. In order to serve these ads, Google Adsense uses DoubleClick DART cookies. When users visit HIF and either view or click an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher’s site(s) and across the web. [Google’s own privacy policy](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-ww-et-asui&medium=link) states the following:

> * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
>  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
>  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns, please take the time to further read up on Google’s privacy policies.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time in the future. We will not reduce your rights under this privacy policy without notification and your explicit consent.

 _This policy was last updated on June 11, 2011._
